Do you want to say something
Right behind me, hey
The dirt
The English soil
I'm very glad to be here
The Earth is the Lord's and
the fulness thereof
It says
I'm saying it's ours
It was Gerrard Winstanley, who said
'the Earth is a treasury for all'
and here at the Royal Exchange
this has been one of the
concentration points
where the fulness of the Earth
has been brought into the hands
and the transmutation of gold
and this has happened by means of blood
So you look at the pictures
and they are tracing the bar relief
of the Royal Exchange.
This goes back to the 1690s.
And then behind me is the place of gold.
This also goes back to the 1690s
Our present crisis now,
we can go back to the 1690s
to see how the Earth and the fulness thereof
was transmuted into gold
and to a small handful of people
who have expropriated
from around the planet
the fulness of our labors.
From, Africa, Asia, South America.
Into this spot
So I won't say I'm glad to be here,
but I'm glad to be with you.